How's it going?
>> Good. I'm blessed.
>> So, what have the last uh 24 hours or so
been like for you?
>> Um been around a lot of people, a lot of
celebrating with my friends and family
and um a long night and a long travel.
>> What do you think of the facility?
>> I love it. It's beautiful. Yeah, it's my
first time seeing it. So, um yeah, it's
nice.
>> Have you had a chance to meet any of
your new teammates or anyone? I met Ko.
He was out on the field. Um, I just
spoke to him a little bit.
>> What was that conversation like?
>> Just basically told him it was honor to
meet him and that I'll be learning a lot
from him and asking asking him a bunch
of questions.
>> What did you ask him?
>> He didn't ask me anything.
>> Oh my god.
>> What did you ask?
>> Oh, I told him I was going to ask him a
ton of questions leading into, you know,
meeting room, whatever it was. Um, I'm
just going to try to learn as much as I
can from him.
>> How familiar are you with his with his
game?
>> Fairly, you know, from his, you know,
Chicago days. Um, there's no way you
would just play football on social media
without seeing a few clips of Killa Max.
So,
>> what kind of questions are you going to
ask him? Like, what what are you most
excited to learn from somebody like
that?
>> Really, he's been in the game so long,
right? So, how he's done that, how he
takes care of his body really, what's
his his routine when it comes to
day-to-day things. And then when it when
we're in the meeting room, um you know,
his pass rush plan, his plan on first
and second down, how he approaches
different looks on the field, just
trying to pick his brain as much as I
can.
>> Jim and Joe, yesterday mentioned just
about your motor and just your
relentlessness. Just what where does
that come from? And what what about your
mentality? mentality allows you to play
that way.
>> I think it just that's just how was how
I've always played the game. Um, growing
up
it was really I didn't really have a
bunch of IQ. I'm 16 years old just
playing football. Um, I always had
awareness for the game and what always
stuck out on the film was my motor and
my relentlessness. So, it's not
something I think about, it's just
something that that happens.
>> You uh decided on a number yet? Um, you
know, I can't get three, but
um, I'll probably just go back to 90, my
um, original college number.
>> Why? Why? Um, I mean, just does it have
any meaning beyond it just being your
original college number?
>> No, it was just the first number I ever
had coming into college. Um, why not go
back to it?
>> And would you try to get three or no?
>> Um,
the odds are kind of zero, but
um, no.
Uh any teammates re reach out to you,
Mario, anybody from uh Miami?
>> Yeah, Coach Chris, JT called me as soon
as I got drafted. Um you know, I still
talk to Ruben and Ahmad every day. So um
yeah, everybody, you know, just congrat
bless you, congratulating me and um
yeah, that's about it.
>> What did it mean for you and Ruben to
both get selected and only seven seven
picks apart?
It's, you know, what we've been working
working like on throughout the past
three years. Um, we talk about it all
the time. We did talk about it all the
time throughout the season. You know,
what we could potentially do. Um, but
you know, when I see when I saw his face
on the TV, um, I really almost shed a
tear. I was so happy he got picked up.
So,
>> who also forgot to say just now, but to
your
>> to your chart is 90.
>> I think Well, I'm not sure. I thought it
they told me it was available. If not,
then
>> if not, I'll I'll just pick another
number. Yeah.
>> You mentioned Coach Taylor at Miami.
What What did you learn from him working
with him?
>> Really, the biggest thing about Coach JT
is he's a simple coach. He's not going
to try to do too much. Like I've watch
like you watch his tape. He's a simple
guy. He, you know, he creates length. He
keeps people away from him and he just
has a high motor. Um that was the
biggest things that stuck out on tape
watching his tape. So and he's the same
way as a coach like you can learn. Every
coach is going to teach you the basic
fundamentals of football. But the
difference between JT and other coaches
is his experience. 14 years in the
league, gold jacket, um picking his
brain on again um how to watch film,
what to look at when you're watching
film. um pass, rush, progression, first
and second down versus third down, how
to take care of my body. Um formation,
everything about football, like the game
is what he taught me the most of.
>> Going to have a a lot of new experiences
here coming days, weeks, months. What
are you most excited about doing?
>> Competing and earning the respect of my
teammates.
>> How do you how do you go about doing
that?
showing up every day on time, ready to
work. Um me, the way what we preach at
Miami, you know, my last four years,
early is on time. So, I always show up
early, take care of my body, do
everything I have to do pre-practice,
and then once you get on that field or
in that weight room, compete your butt
off, and you know, people respect guys
who compete and work their butt off. So,
just do that and earn the respect of my
coaches and my teammates.
What was that moment like when your
phone started vibrating last night to
ring?
>> My heart dropped. I was just
I was excited. I knew it was that time.
Picked up the phone. Coach Harbaugh was
on the phone, talked to me. Um basically
said they they really liked my formal
meeting at the combine and
yeah, it was just everything else was
really a blur. I was just it was yes
sirs and thank yous just and then yeah
man I'm just ready to be here excited to
be here.
>> Is there anything about the the whole
process since obviously you thought
about it for a long time but like is
there anything that was surprising to
you how quickly you got here? How did
this happen? I know it's been a
whirlwind like anything you didn't
expect?
>> No, nothing I didn't expect. You hear a
bunch of different stories from people
who got picked up. Um, so throughout
this whole process going from last game
into training preparation to combine to
pro day to 30 visits to draft day to
coming here. Um, you hear all about it.
So nothing came to nothing came to like
came to me as a surprise.
>> Coach Harbaugh talked yesterday about
how you know you love to practice, love
to play. Why why do you love football?
>> Why do I love football?
I just love the game. I don't It's like
if I asked you why you love pizza, you
just love it. You know,
you know, it's the game I've been
playing since I was 8 years old. Um the
physicality, the violence, the
technical, like how technical I am in my
game. Um just everything that comes with
football on the field and off the field,
the relationships you can build. Um
football is more than just helmet and
pads. It's like it's a lifestyle for me.
Were you always a a defensive player on
that side of the ball? No,
>> I've played I played one I played a
little bit of tight end. Um I played a
year at I play a little bit of receiver.
Um but 90% of my time has always been on
defense.
>> So you seem very calm and collected.
What happens to you when you step on
that football team?
>> I'm not going to lie, it's just it's not
something I think about. It's just the
way I've been I've played the game my
whole life. It's not a switch that I
flip. It's not something that I get on
the field and have to convince myself to
do. It's it's just the way the game is
played to me. Um and it's the way it's
always been played.
>> Just uh talked about Khalil, but you're
also joining a room with Tuli Palotu.
How familiar are you with his game, if
at all?
>> I'm not very familiar, but I'm going
watch a ton of film. I love watch sorry
I love watching football so I'll
familiarize myself really quick.
>> He's a guy that like you can move inside
and rush over guards Khil stuff so you
can pretty much rush from anywhere.
>> What do you think you're going to bring
in terms of some of the interchangeable
pieces up front and having a bunch of
guys in the room that you know like you
rush from the edge and rush from the
interior. What do you think that's going
to provide?
>> I think I'm adding another really good
piece to that D line. Um, of course the
versatility that I'm able to rush inside
and out, but also the size and violence
that I play with where I can set an edge
on first and second down, a blunt edge.
Um, so I think I'm a well-rounded
defensive player, and you know, I'm just
excited to go out there and compete with
them boys.
>> In terms of your moves and your your
pass rush bag, your toolbox, was there a
moment in your college career where you
really started to hone different moves?
was more of a process over your entire
college career building that
>> I've changed it throughout the years. Um
like I've used to I used to rely a lot
on a chop like a chop dip rip but then I
started facing old linemen who who are
double punchers that punch pretty high
and it's hard to chop a high hand. So I
kind of transitioned to using a side
scissor and just trying different things
out. Um, like I spend a lot of time at
the facility alone just trying to learn
um my body, my steps, how long it takes
for me to get to the fight line, where
I'm making a move on the tackle, um,
rush angles, sorry, um, width, from how
far I am from, wherever I'm rushing. Um,
so I've done a ton of different stuff
alone where I practice what moves I want
to use, but it's my bag has gotten
better throughout the years to where I
can use a bunch of different moves. Are
you the type of guy that's watching a
lot of like NFL edges and trying to take
what they do and implement it into your
game or are you more so like you're
saying sort of on the flip yourself
trying to figure out what works for you
personally?
>> No, I take I take I take stuff from
everybody. Like Ruben is younger than
me. When he came in as a freshman, I was
a true senior. Um I took stuff from
Ruben. Like if I see it and I see that
it works and I like it, I'll put it into
my game. the way the way I run a T game
or one one of our stunts where the
tackle penetrates and the the DN sells
speed and loops behind him. I seen one
of our D tackles run like penetrate a
certain way where he was attacking the
tackle rather than the guard and the way
he was using his hands and I'm like it
worked and I see it worked like I told
myself I like that so I stole that and
put into my game. So I'm always like I'm
stealing everybody else's move and
putting into mine and making it mine I
guess.
What was the interaction like with you
and coach Harpal when you showed up to
the facility today?
>> W very welcoming. Um he had a big smile.
I had a big smile. I'm I'm typically
always smiling. Um but it was, you know,
a heartwarming welcome.
>> What uh what should the fans expect from
you? What are you going to show?
>> What should they expect from
>> Yeah. What are they what are they going
to see? What would you tell the fans
that you're going to bring to the table?
>> I'm bringing versatility. I'm bringing a
pastor's bag and violence and the
ability to set a blunt edge.